The school is full of whispers The halls are full
of filth They teach them things I'll never say
They'll rot them all with guilt They talk about
those bodies And the dirty things they do But I
will never let that poison ever get to you
INAPPROPRIATE! I check the box, I sign the line
INAPPROPRIATE! Your mind will stay as pure as
mine. You do not need to know those things,
you'll never leave my sight. I'll keep you safe,
I'll keep you clean, I'll keep you in the light.
You're not like other children. You're fragile
and you're small. You do not need those
questions. You don't need them at all. Why talk
about relations? Why talk about desire? It's
just a fire for the weak. I'll protect you from
that fire. Appropriate! I checked the box, I
signed the line.
You're my old state, as pure as vine. You do not
need to know the things, you'll never leave my
sight. I'll keep you safe, I'll keep you clean,
I'll keep you in the light.
Family life What bodies do They're changing
forms The books they read The words they use
It's all
I check the box, I sign the line
Your mind will stay as pure as mine You do not need
to know those things You'll never leave my sight
I'll keep you safe, I'll keep you clean I'll keep
you in the light
Inappropriate